Guide to the New York State Council on the Arts Electronic Media and Film Program records, [ca. 1960-2011]
New York State Council on the Arts Electronic Media and Film Program records
- Individuals A-Z
  - S-Z
    - Stein, Carol and Susan Wittenberg - Film and Video Workshop (VN 225), c. 1994 (Box 14, Folder 42)
      Grant application FY94 for Insomnia
    - Stein, Doug - CSC Repertory, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 43)
      Grant application 1990-1991 for The Resistible Rise Arturo UI
    - Steinfeld, Ellen, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 44)
      final report (FY83-84) for relief sculpture
    - Stephens, Bill - Media Process, Peoples Communication Network, undated (Box 14, Folder 45)
      Project description for Manhattanland Grant Company
    - Stern, Peggy - Film News Now (VD 216), 1986-1987 (Box 14, Folder 46)
      Grant application 1986-1987 for Senior Year; correspondence
    - Stiles - Akwesasne (VN 96), c. 1984 (Box 14, Folder 47)
      Grant application 1984-1985 for videos for the Akwesasne Museum and Cultural Center Inc.
    - Stoney, George - NYFA (VD 228), undated (Box 14, Folder 48)
      Grant application (undated) for The Uprising of '34
    - Sturgeon, John - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute (VA 55), c. 1985 (Box 14, Folder 49)
      Grant application 1985-1986 for I thought I was...
    - Suleiman, Elia and Jayce Salloum - CEPA (VA 176), 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 50)
      Grant application (1989-1990, 1990) for Muquadimma Lynihaiyat Jidaal Intifada: Speaking for oneself... and Wa Hakadha Tamurru 'L-Ayyam (And So the Days Pass); letter of agreement
    - Sullivan, Kaylynn - Creative Time, Inc. (7-8), c. 1984 (Box 14, Folder 51)
      Grant application 1984-1985 for Nightstrippers
    - Sumter, Ellen - Concerned Black Filmmakers of NY (FN 254), c. 1990 (Box 14, Folder 52)
      Grant application 1990 for Savannah
    - Sun, Carol - Art in General (PA 270), 1990 (Box 14, Folder 53)
      Grant application 1990-1991 for China Mary, A History of Immigration and Assimilation of Chinese Women; letter of agreement
    - Sunde, Christian, undated (Box 14, Folder 54)
      Project proposal for Adirondack Panorama
    - Suzan, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Switzgable, Meg - Film Fund, Inc., c. 1984 (Box 14, Folder 56)
      Grant application 1984-1985 for Passing Through Linden; letter of agreement
    - Tajiri, Rea - Asian Cinevision (VD 485), c.1989-1999 (Box 14, Folder 57)
      Grant application (1989-1990, 1991-1992, FY96) for History and Memory, Yuri Kochiyama: Catalyst for Human Rights and Strawberry Fields; letter of agreement (1995, 1998); final report FY 1998-1999 for The Family Body
    - Tajima, Renee - Film News Now (VD 222), c. 1992 (Box 14, Folder 58)
      Grant application 1992-1993 for The Asian Americans
    - Takagi, JT Orinne - Camera News (VN 204), c. 1987-1996 (Box 14, Folder 59)
      Grant application (1987-1988, 1991-1992, FY94, FY96) for Homes Apart: The Two Koreas, #7 To Main Street, Faithful Daughter and Legs Like Turnips; letter of agreement (1991)
    - Takazauckas, Albert - Downtown Art Company (DI 95), c. 1994 (Box 14, Folder 60)
      Grant application 1994-1995 for Heros and Saints
    - Tann, Hilary - Schenectady Symphony Orchestra (OR 234), c. 1986-1988 (Box 14, Folder 61)
      Grant application (undated) for music composition; letter of agreement (1986-1988)
    - Taylor, Cecil (CH 213), 1987 (Box 14, Folder 62)
      Project description for music composition; letter of agreement
    - Taylor, Jocelyn - Women Make Movies (VA 283), c. 1995 (Box 14, Folder 63)
      Grant application FY95 for Bodily Functions
    - Taylor, Joshua - Other Pictures (VD 199), c. 1998 (Box 14, Folder 64)
      Grant application FY98 for Dita
    - Tcimpidis, David - Delaware Valley Arts Alliance (CH 82), 1997 (Box 14, Folder 65)
      CV for David Tcimpidis; letter of agreement
    - Teitelbaum, Richard - Music From Japan (EL 82), c. 1987, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 66)
      Grant application (1987-1988, FY92) for Golem Speak and unnamed music composition; letter of agreement; description and diagram for Concerto Grosso
    - Telson, Robert, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 67)
      Letter of agreement for Book of Love
    - Templeton, Fiona - Art Awareness, Inc. (PW 52) (PE 157), c. 1987, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 68)
      Grant application (1987-1988, 1996-1997) for You-The City, A city-wide play for an audience of one and Realities
    - Thistlethwaite, Polly - Alternative Media Information Center (VD 232), 1991 (Box 14, Folder 69)
      Grant application (undated) for Lesbian History: not Just Passing Through; letter of agreement
    - Thoj, Va-Megn - Camera News, Inc. (VN 213), c. 1997 (Box 14, Folder 70)
      Grant application FY97 for Pledge of Allegiance
    - Thomas, Augusta Read - Syracuse Society for New Music (CH 76) (IND), undated (Box 14, Folder 71)
      Sample of work submitted form; Biography of Augusta Read Thomas
    - Thorne, Nicholas - 92nd Street Y, undated (Box 14, Folder 72)
    - Thornton, Leslie - Drift Distribution (VE 238) (IND), c. 1985, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 73)
      Grant application (1985-1986, FY94) for Peggy and Fred in Hell and The Great Invisible; letter of the agreement
    - Thorington, Helen - New Radio and Performing Arts (SC 83), 1985-1997 (Box 14, Folder 74)
      Grant application (1985-1986, undated, FY92, FY95) for Building the Universe, untitled sound composition and North Country; letter of agreement (1985, 1997)
    - Thorsen, Karen - NYFA (VD 138), c. 1987-1989 (Box 14, Folder 75)
      Grant application (1987-1988, 1989-1990) for James Baldwin Today: Encounters with the Next Generation; letter of agreement
    - Thouard, Sylvie - Film News Now (VN 29), c. 1984 (Box 14, Folder 76)
      Grant application 1984-1985 for Theater in Prison
    - Threadgill, Henry - Bang on a Can (CH 78) (IND), 1995 (Box 14, Folder 77)
      Letter of agreement; CV for Henry Threadgill
    - Threadgill, Henry - Wooster Group (SF 119) (IND), 1993 (Box 14, Folder 78)
      Grant application (undated) for Improvisors Unlimited; letter of agreement
    - Tillman, Lynne - Woman Make Movies (FN 224), 1986 (Box 14, Folder 79)
      Grant application 1986-1987 for Two Serious Ladies; letter of agreement
    - Tipton, Jennifer - Wooster Group, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 80)
      Grant application 1990-1991 for Brace Up!; letter of agreement
    - Tiranoff, Louise - Icarus Endeavor (VD 176), 1985 (Box 14, Folder 81)
      Grant application 1985-186 for My One and Only; letter of agreement
    - Toepp, Wayne (PA 158), c. 1987 (Box 14, Folder 82)
      Grant application 1987-1988 for Capitol Proscenium Series; letter of agreement
    - Toman, Mary Ann - Film News Now (VE 258), c. 1987, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 83)
      Grant application (1987-1988, 1990) for Island of Symmetry and The Female Offender; letter of agreement
    - Tomney, Ed (AA 215), c. 1988 (Box 14, Folder 84)
      Grant application 1988-1989 for Seismic Room Intoner; panel comments
    - Tone, Yasunao - Harvestworks, Inc. (NT 216), c. 1996 (Box 14, Folder 85)
      Grant application FY96 for Musica Simulacra - CD-ROM Project
    - Tong, Nancy - Film News Now (VD 240) (IND), c. 1994 (Box 14, Folder 86)
      Grant application FY94 for Remember Nanjing 1937; letter of agreement
    - Torikai, Ushio - Experimental Intermedia (EL 123), 1990, 1997, undated (Box 14, Folder 87)
      Grant application (FY90) for music composition; final report FY 1997-1998 for Still/Four; project description for (Torres) Paths of Glory; letter of agreement
    - Torres, Francesc - Parabola Arts Foundation (VA 232), 1986 (Box 14, Folder 88)
      Grant application 1986-1987 for Everybody's House is Burning; letter of agreement
    - Tropicana, Carmelita and Eileen Myles - Hallwalls (CO 84), c. 1994 (Box 14, Folder 89)
      Grant application 1994-1995 for unnamed project on the life of Sor Juana
    - Troyano, Ela - Media Network (VN 210), c. 1987-2001 (Box 14, Folder 90)
      Grant application (1987-1988, 1989-1990, 1990, FY96, FY01) for film about Carmelita Tropicana, Los Hijos de Concha, Once Upon a Time in the Bronx, Latin Boys Go to Hell and La Lupe; letter of agreement (1990, 1995)
    - Tsontakis, George - Newband (CH 84), 1997 (Box 14, Folder 91)
    - Tsuno, Keiko - Basement Workshop (VN 7), c. 1985, undated (Box 14, Folder 92)
      Grant application (1985-1986, undated) for a film project on the Vietnamese orphans from the Vietnam War and Citizen 13660
    - Tucker, Toba - Catskill Center of Photography (EF 181), c. 1986 (Box 14, Folder 93)
      Grant application 1986-1987 for Portraits of the Shinnecock Indians
    - Tudor, David- Cunningham and Cage (S 31d), undated (Box 14, Folder 94)
    - Tue, Liane Tee - Henry Street Settlement, c. 1992 (Box 14, Folder 95)
      Grant application 1992-1993 for Lion Bridge Tavern
    - Tyler, Edwina Lee (SC 228), undated (Box 14, Folder 96)
      Grant application (undated) for Song of Lawino; letter of agreement
    - Tyranny, Blue Gene - Roulette Intermedium (CV 85), 1990, 1997-1998, undated (Box 14, Folder 97)
      Grant application (undated, FY90) for unnamed music composition and The Electrical Matter; letter of agreement; final report form FY 1997-1998
    - Tzouras-Bosmajian, Vilka, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 98)
      Correspondence, letter of agreement
    - Ukeles, Mierle Laderman - NYFA (SC 161), c. 1988-1990 (Box 14, Folder 99)
      Grant application (1989-1990, 1990-1991) for Media Flow Wall and Air/Earth/Water: A Second Turn; letter of agreement; panel comments
    - Unbekant, Lauren - Contemporary Theater of Syracuse (CT 55), c. 1996-1997 (Box 14, Folder 100)
      Grant application 1996-997 for The Way; final report form FY 1996-1997; letter of agreement
    - Unger, Mary Ann - Cityarts Workshop, Inc. (OS 168), c. 1985 (Box 14, Folder 101)
      Grant application 1985-1986 for Garden Temples
    - Ueno, Watoku - Yara Arts Group, Inc (DE 54), c. 1992, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 102)
      Grant application (1992-1993, 1996-1997) for Blind Sight and Virtual Souls
    - Vail, Pegi (Peggy), undated (Box 14, Folder 103)
      panel comments; CV for Pegi Veil
    - Valadez, John - Alternative Media Information Center (VD 206), c. 1998 (Box 14, Folder 104)
      Grant application FY98 for On the Border
    - Vasiliewsi, Valeria, undated (Box 14, Folder 105)
      biography of Valeria Wasilewski; project description for Song of Lawino
    - Vazquez, Blanca and Portillo - Alternative Media Information Center (VD 187), c. 1991 (Box 14, Folder 106)
      Grant application 1991-1992 for Fighting for Our Lives
    - Vega, Ed - Medicine Show Ensemble, c. 1992 (Box 14, Folder 107)
      Grant application 1992-1993 for Columbus Discovers the Sitar, the Tabla and Curry: A Historical Divergence
    - Velez, Edin - Electronic Arts Intermix (VA 186), c. 1987, 1989, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 108)
      Grant application (1987-1988, 1989-1990) for Naruhodo, Event Window and Signal to Noise; letter of agreement; lawsuit decision (1993)
    - Velez, Glen - INTAR (ST 124) (IND), 1993 (Box 14, Folder 109)
    - Venuto, Maria - Standby (VA 295) (IND), 1995 (Box 14, Folder 110)
      Grant application FY95 fot The Tourist; letter of agreement
    - Vierk, Lois V. - Experimental Intermedia Foundation (CH 243), c. 1992 (Box 14, Folder 111)
      Grant application (FY92, undated) for music composition
    - Volkes, Ann (VD 220), 1988 (Box 14, Folder 112)
      Grant application 1988-1989 for Lee Grant: Definitions of an Independent Woman; letter of agreement
    - Von Heflin, Kirk (VD 104), 1985-1988 (Box 14, Folder 113)
      Grant application (1985-1986, 1988-1989)for Que Viva Mexico; correspondence; letter of agreement
    - Wada, Yoshi - Experimental Intermedia Foundation (SD 89), c. 1985-1992 (Box 14, Folder 114)
      Grant application (1985-1986, 1989-1990, FY92) for music/sound composition
    - Waggoner, Andrew - Open Hand Theater (ST 82) (IND), undated (Box 14, Folder 115)
      Sample of work submitted form; CV for Andrew Waggoner
    - Wagner, Melinda J. - Westchester Philharmonic (CH 88), c. 1997 (Box 14, Folder 116)
      final report form (undated); letter of agreement; CV for Melinda Wagner
    - Wagoner, James (CV 47), 1987 (Box 14, Folder 117)
      Sample of work submitted form; biography of James Wagoner; letter of agreement
    - Waletzky, Josh - Upstate Films (VD 228), undated (Box 14, Folder 118)
      single handwritten note
    - Wallace, Stewart - Ontological-Hysteric Theater (ST 84) (IND), undated (Box 14, Folder 119)
      biography of Stewart Wallace
    - Walworth, Dan - Artists Space (VE 234), 1986-1987 (Box 14, Folder 120)
      Grant application 1986-1987 for untitled film project; letter of agreement
    - Ward, Peter - Pauline Oliveros Foundation, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 121)
    - Warren, Tom, 1982, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 122)
      NEA grant application 1984-1985 for unnamed project; letter of agreement (1982)
    - Warshaw, Andrew, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 123)
    - Wasser, Deborah - Media Network (VD 299) (IND), 1994, undated (Box 14, Folder 124)
      Grant application (undated) for Legacy, letter of agreement
    - Wasserman, Suzanne, undated (Box 14, Folder 125)
      CV for Suzanne Wasserman
    - Watkins, Peter (F 171D), 1983 (Box 14, Folder 126)
      Letter of agreement (1983); also located in this folder Jack Waters: grant application for The Ring MY Way; letter of agreement (1990)
    - Watson, Eric - Theater for Hudson Highlands (JZ 131), c. 1990 (Box 14, Folder 127)
      Grant application FY90 for Further than the Truth
    - Weems, Marianne - Performance Zone, Inc. (DI 58), c. 1989, 1992, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 128)
      Grant application (1989-1990, 1992-1993, 1996-1997) for play based on Hedda Gabler, Evidence and Imperial Motel (Faust)
    - Weil, Brian - Exit Art (PH 124), 1990 (Box 14, Folder 129)
      Grant application c. 1990 for A.I.D.S. A traveling exhibition of photographs; letter of agreement
    - Weinbren, Grahame - Black Maria (VA 281), c. 1987 (Box 14, Folder 130)
      Grant application 1987-1988 for Circumstantial Distortions; letter of agreement
    - Weinstein, David - Roulette Extramedia (A 31), undated (Box 14, Folder 131)
      Sample of work submitted form; CV for David Weinstein
    - Weiss, Andrea - Jezebel Productions (PD 209), 1990, undated (Box 14, Folder 132)
      Grant application (1990, undated) for One Way Ticket and Seed of Sarah; letter of agreement
    - Weissman, Dan (VD 277), 1988 (Box 14, Folder 133)
      Grant application 1988-1989 for Terezin Diary; press release; letter of agreement
    - Wellman, Mac - Shaliko Company (89-024), undated (Box 14, Folder 134)
      CV for Mac Wellman; letter of intent
    - Wen, Laurie - Women Make Movies (VD 218), . 1996 (Box 14, Folder 135)
      Grant application FY96 for Don't Worry I'm Fine
    - Whitely, Sara (VA 224), c. 1996 (Box 14, Folder 136)
      Grant application FY96 for Osmosis
    - Wiechmann, Barbara - Theater Labrador (WS045) (IND), c. 1998 (Box 14, Folder 137)
      Grant application 1998-1999 for The Triangle Project
    - Wieselman, Doug - En Garde Arts (ST 86) (IND), c. 1995-1996 (Box 14, Folder 138)
      Grant application FY96 for music composition; final project report FY 1995-1996
    - Wilcox, Ronald - Center for Photography at Woodstock (PH 183), c. 1989 (Box 14, Folder 139)
      Grant application FY89 for Interplay: The Visual/The Vernal
    - Wilks, Talvin - Gotham Dance (WS046) (IND), 1999 (Box 14, Folder 140)
      Correspondence; biography of Talvin Wilks
    - Williams, Brooks - Byrdcliffe Performing Arts Center (SD 252), 1988 (Box 14, Folder 141)
    - Williams, Marco (VD 281), c. 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 142)
      Grant application (1986-1987, 1988-1989) for In Search for Our Fathers; letter of agreement
    - Williams Merce and Roger Phenix - Columbia University (VD 180), c. 1985 (Box 14, Folder 143)
      Grant application 1985-1986 for I Have a Good Mind
    - Williams, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 144)
      Letter of agreement (1999) - signature of artist is hard to read
    - Williams, Rebecca - Women Make Movies (VN 251) (IND), c. 1994 (Box 14, Folder 145)
      Grant application FY94 for Sugar on the Floor
    - Wilson, Dana - Arts for Greater Rochester (CH 87) (IND), undated (Box 14, Folder 146)
    - Wilson, Roy (VN 283), c. 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 147)
      Grant application (19867-1988, 1988-1989) for Hunger; letter of agreement
    - Windish, Joe - Alternative Media Information Center (VD 253), c. 1989 (Box 14, Folder 148)
      Grant application (undated) for Twenty-One; letter of agreement
    - Wineapple, Patty - Women Make Movies (VD 211), (1986)1997 (Box 14, Folder 149)
      Grant application FY98 for Beyond Pigs and Bunnies: The John and Faith Hubley Story; IRS tax exempt status letter for Women Make Movies; project update
    - Winer, Lucy - Women Make Movies (VD 254) (IND), c. 1988, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 150)
      Grant application (1988-1989, FY94) for I am Jesus: The Tale of an Exhausted Woman and Art as Autobiography
    - Witsiepe, Bruce - ABC No Rio (GR 186), 1989 (Box 14, Folder 151)
      Grant application FY98 for Anti Utopia/ artist/portfolio; letter of agreement
    - Wittenberg, Susan - Film and Video Workshop (GR 176), c. 1990 (Box 14, Folder 152)
      Grant application (undated) for Susan and Susan posters; correspondence
    - Wladimir Herman - Association for Development of Dramatic Arts, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 153)
      Project description for The Shoemakers
    - Wodiczko, Krzysztof - Exit Art (SC 170), c. 1987 (Box 14, Folder 154)
      Grant application 1987-1988 for The Homeless Vehicle
    - Wojl, Ira - NYFA (VD 213), c. 1998 (Box 14, Folder 155)
      Grant application FY98 for Best Man
    - Wong, Willi - Film News Now Foundation (VD 257), undated (Box 14, Folder 156)
      Grant application (undated) for Unclaimed; letter of agreement
    - Woolf, Randall - American Music Center (SC 93) (VAP), undated (Box 14, Folder 157)
      Sample of work submitted form; biography of Randall Woolf
    - Wooster, Ann Sargent - Experimental Television Center (VA 240), 1985 (Box 14, Folder 158)
      Grant application 1985-1986 for Carmenx3; letter of agreement
    - World Saxophone Quartet - BAM (JZ 1), c. 1989 (Box 14, Folder 159)
      Sample of work submitted form; biography of World Saxophone Quartet; letter of agreement
    - Worsley, Dale, Boothe, and Charles Dodge - Hallwalls (PE 179), undated (Box 14, Folder 160)
      Grant application (undated) doe Hoy (In Her Memory)
    - Wright, David, undated (Box 14, Folder 161)
      biography of David Wright
    - Wuorinen, Charles - Lincoln Center (CH 135) (IND), undated (Box 14, Folder 162)
      Sample of work submitted form; biography of Charles Wuorinen; letter of agreement
    - Yanagisawa, Deborah, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 163)
    - Yankowitz, Susan - The St. Ann Center, c. 1992 (Box 14, Folder 164)
      Grant application 1992-1993 for unnamed play commission
    - Yi, Chen (CH 233), undated (Box 14, Folder 165)
      Project description for music composition; sample of work submitted form; biography for Chen Yi
    - Yim, Jay Alan - Andiamo Chamber Ensemble (CH 257), c. 1989 (Box 14, Folder 166)
      Grant application FY89 for music composition; panel comments
    - Young, LaMonte - MELA (EL 136), 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 167)
      Grant application FY90 for music composition; letter of agreement; correspondence
    - Younger, Robert - The Queens Museum (IS 182), c. 1985 (Box 14, Folder 168)
      Grant application 1985-1986 for Holmesinoning/Wissinburg
    - Zablotny, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 169)
      Project report for Dorthy Day documentary
    - Zando, Julie - Squeaky Wheel (VA 259), c. 1989-1991 (Box 14, Folder 170)
      Grant application (1988-1989, undated) for 3 Case Histories and The Apparent Trap; letter of agreement (undated, 1991)
    - Zelevansky, Paul, undated (Box 14, Folder 171)
      plans for publicizing and documenting the work form for a video/story in disc form for home computer for Book II of The Case for the Burial of Ancestors
    - Zellnik, David, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 172)
      mailing list; correspondence regarding Kidnapping Kipling
    - Zhao, Sui Kang - Jamaica Arts Center (AI 311), c. 1995 (Box 14, Folder 173)
      Grant application FY95 for video art installation
    - Zhou, Quinru - Music From China (CH 89) (IND), undated (Box 14, Folder 174)
      biography for Quinru Zhou
    - Ziv, Ilan (VD 233), 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 175)
      Grant application 1988-1989 for Kitsch of Death; project update; progress report; letter of agreement
    - Zorn, John - Haleaka (SF 138), c. 1990, 1992, undated (Box 14, Folder 176)
      Grant application (FY90) for music composition
    - Zrnic, Maja - Icarus Endeavor (VD 262), c. 1992, undated (Box 14, Folder 177)
      Grant application (1992-1993, undated) for Holy Virginity and Nana; letter of agreement
    - Zurkow, Marina - PS122 (VE 209), c. 1992 (Box 14, Folder 178)
      Grant application FY92 for A Travelogue of Fossils
    - Zwickler, Phil - Realis Pictures, Inc. (VD 296), 1987, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 179)
      Grant application (1987-1988, FY91) for Rights and Reactions and Voices From the Front; letter of agreement
    - Empty Artist Folders
      These artist folders were found empty within the collection: Akalaitis, JoAnne - Mabou Mines, (VN 4); Alonso, Ana Coyne; Arlyck, Ralph; Batsry, Irit; Berg, Allison; Beroes, Stephanie - Collective for Living Cinema (VE 16); Bertelson, Phil; Bertololotto, Caterina (PE 12); Beyer, Regina - New Radio and Performing Arts (RA 27) (IND); Bie;awa, Lisa; Billingsley, Scott - Collab (VN 13); Blane, Marc; Blaustein, Susan - Parnassus (C 115);Bloom, Jane Ira; Blum, Joshua - Media Network (VD 30); Bonney, Anney; Botein, Emily (54 First Place, Brooklyn, NY 11231); Brown, Jim; Bunkley, Brit; Buckingham, Matthew - Millenium (VE 40); Buvoli, Luca; Byron, Don - Bang on a Can (CH 7); Cammisa, Rebecca; Carlos, Laurie - BACA Downtown; Cohen, Debby Lee - International Cultural Program (VA 53); Cohen, Douglas - Center for Exploratory and Perceptual (SC 9); Connor, Maureen; Cora, Tom - Harvestworks (SF 9) (IND);Coston, Peter; Courtney, Erin - Clubbed Thumb (WS008) (IND); Cramer, Tim Medicine Show (ST 122) (IND); Custer, Calvin - Syracuse Society for New Music (CH 91); Danielpour, Richard - Concert Artists Guild (SI 11) (IND); Davis, Russell - New York Theater Workshop; De Jong, Constance; DeRuiter, Heidi; Dobson, Daniel; Dolin, Philip; du Plessis, Nancy; Dwyer, Nancy; Eckert, Rinde - Foundry Theater (SC 17); Egass, Eric; Elliot, Jonathan; Elros, Bradley - Ocula; Fekuer; Goldwin, Liz; Gompertz, Jeff; Harberg, Amanda; Harrow, Nancy; Hayes, Doris - NYFA; Henrich, Biff; Huey, Victoey W. (5-7 Doyers Streey, NY, NY); Jamal, Ahmad; Jenkins, Amy; Kilberg, Richard - Cine Information (VD 130); King, Mike; Krakower, David; Kreitzer, Carson- NYFA (WS023) (IND); Lambort, Alix; Lederman, Faye; Legere, Phoebe; Maggio, Joe; Mamlox, Ursula; McCleave, Leslie; Miller, Branda; Miller, Rebecca - NYFA (VD 134); Miralda; Montague, Sarah; Musto, JOhn - Conert Artists Guild (CV 79); Nelson, Richard - Manhattan Theater Club; Neshat, Shirin; Nicard, Gary (MD 110); Pak, Greg; Parker, William; Post, Gardner; Rathsmann, Brigit; Reddy, Rob; Rowe, Hahn; Sandler, Eve; Schlemowitz, Joel;Schlanger, Matthew - Experimental Television Arts Center (VA 25); Smith, Alan; Smith, Mimi; Sobel, Nina; Spiro, Ellen - Hallwalls (VD 174); Spleth, Tom; Stephan, Donald; Tahara, R.; Tieghman, D. Van/ Buchen - Sonic Architecture (CO 184) Note Reads "12 Slides"; Vanouse, Paul; Von Ancken, David; Wagoner, Jane; Waters, Jack - ABC No Rio (PE 169); Wong, Mel; Zhuang, Liu; Zaldivar, Juan Carlos Martinez
- Reports and Catalogs
  - What People Think of Television and Other Mass Media 1959-1972, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Reports, 1978 (Box 15, Volume 1)